[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Where were you, when did you hear, and what were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I was at home, I was reading a book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "I think that's a dangerous presumption, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Very dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Actually had him face his accusers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "No, I think this worked out about as well as it could work out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "When you walk around New York today, what reaction are you getting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "People are very happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "How do you think overall history will judge him and America's relationship with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I think he's going to be viewed as one of the great monsters of history.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Mr. Blair, when did you hear the news that bin Laden was dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I heard it in the very early hours of the morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Blair"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Did you ever think this day would come?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Well, you know, I think I -- when I first thought about it, I was sure it would happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Should we be making more effort there now than perhaps we have been in the last few months?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "EX", "RB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, I think the -- the problem is, Piers, that this is an issue all over this region and beyond.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Have you spoken to President Bush since the news of bin Laden's death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "We've been in touch actually together, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Laden"], "PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Bob Woodward, is this a spectacular triumph for Barack Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "It seems to be, because you see his caution.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Woodward", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "I mean it's about as good as it gets, isn't it, for a covert operation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Did you believe that the death of bin Laden vindicates the policy in relation to Afghanistan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Probably does not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "I mean if that's the case, should we speed up the withdrawal of troops from Afghanistan and get where the action seems to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, that's the question in the next couple of months that President Obama is going to face.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Woodward"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "And can we apply the pressure so they will do some of the things against the al Qaeda leadership so we don't have to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Bob Woodward, thank you very much indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Senator, a pretty good day for President Obama, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "It's a very good day for our country, but it's also a terrific day for the president who made a very gutsy, very tough presidential decision, and it worked out, and I think the country and the world are better off because of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "What do you think the honest answer is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, the honest answer is that it's very, very difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Now that he has been eliminated and al Qaeda's presence in Afghanistan seems to be massively lower than it was, is this the signal for the end of the war in Afghanistan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "It's a signal for the beginning of a transition, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Qaeda", "Afghanistan", "Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Senator, tell me exactly what went through your mind the moment you heard that bin Laden had been killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, I felt pretty good about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gettysburg"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "And then reality sets in because I heard some commentators say this is the end of the war on terror, which struck me as a pretty fatuous thing to say because it clearly isn't, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "No, as I said, I believe it's the Saratoga or the Gettysburg.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "CD", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What's been your reaction to the death of Osama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, this morning I -- it was -- I relived everything; 9/11 came to my mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "And how difficult has it been for you to be a bin Laden?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "IN LADEN: Well, I have not heard that any of the family has renounced their name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What kind of man was he when you met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Very religious man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Do you think they will be in mourning today, or will there be members that are happy that he's now dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "My understanding of the Saudi society is that I'm sure they are mourning because for them it's their brother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Who do you think may have been helping him financially over the last few years, because clearly somebody was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, I think that -- my understanding of the Saudi law, you can not disinherit a person who is a good Muslim.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George W. Bush"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "When you first heard that bin Laden was dead, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "First of all, I was grateful for the resolute that George W. Bush brought for the effort.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andy"]}, "docId": "110502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How do you see the next few months playing out now that we've actually seen the back of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, I think I join Andy and probably every American saying it's been a gratifying 24 hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]